export let easyQuestions = [
{
        question: "What is Micheal's full name?",
        answer1: "A) Michael Nicholas Myers",
        answer2: "B) Michael Audrey Myers",
        answer3: "C) Michael Donald Myers",
        answer4: "D) Michael Will Myers",
        correctAnswer: 2

    },
    {
        question: "When is Micheal's birthday?",
        answer1: "A) October 25th, 1957",
        answer2: "B) October 27th, 1957",
        answer3: "C) October 19th, 1957",
        answer4: "D) October 31st, 1957",
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What kind of killer is Micheal?",
        answer1: "A) Mass Murderer",
        answer2: "B) Psychotic Killer",
        answer3: "C) Hedonistic killer",
        answer4: "D) None of the above",
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Whats Michael`s father`s name?",
        answer1: "A) Peter",
        answer2: "B) Ron",
        answer3: "C) Don",
        answer4: "D) Dan",
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Whats Michael`s mothers`s name?",
        answer1: "A) Edith",
        answer2: "B) Deborah",
        answer3: "C) Audrey",
        answer4: "D) Judith",
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What was the name of the older sister he killed? ",
        answer1: "A) Edith",
        answer2: "B) Deborah",
        answer3: "C) Audrey",
        answer4: "D) Judith",
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the name of the younger sister he spared?",
        answer1: "A) Edith Strode",
        answer2: "B) Deborah Strode",
        answer3: "C) Laura Ann Strode",
        answer4: "D) Laurie Ann Strode",
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "What year was Halloween released?",
        answer1: "A) 1970",
        answer2: "B) 1978",
        answer3: "C) 1984",
        answer4: "D) 1990",
        correctAnswer: 2
    }, 
    {
        question: "What was the name of the little boy Laurie was babysitting?",
        answer1: "A) Tommy",
        answer2: "B) Joey",
        answer3: "C) Jimmy",
        answer4: "D) Bobby",
        correctAnswer: 1
    }, 
    {
        question: "What kind of doctor was Sam Loomis?",
        answer1: "A) Surgeon",
        answer2: "B) Psychiatrist",
        answer3: "C) Lawyer",
        answer4: "D) Phlosopher",
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What was used to kill Judith Myers?",
        answer1: "A) A Kitchen Knife",
        answer2: "B) A Chainsaw",
        answer3: "C) A Swiss Army Knife",
        answer4: "D) a Screwdriver",
        correctAnswer: 1
    }
];

